Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Joseph Lindon Smith papers
- Letters, 1768-1965, Series 2:; (Box 1-4, OV 11; 3.5 linear feet)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "G," undated, (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "H" - "J," undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "K" - "M," undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "N" - "R," undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "S," undated, (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "T" - "Z," undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Letters, 1768-1848 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Letters, 1873-1882 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Letters, 1883, (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 21-23)
  - Letters, 1884, (12 folders) (Box 1, Folder 24-35)
  - Letters, 1885, (5 folders) (Box 1, Folder 36-40)
  - Letters, 1886-1890 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Letters, 1891, (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 42-44)
  - Letters, 1892, (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 45-46)
  - Letters, 1893, (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 47-49)
  - Letters, 1894, (10 folders) (Box 1, Folder 50-59)
  - Letters, 1895, (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 60-62)
  - Letters, 1896, (5 folders) (Box 1, Folder 63-67)
  - Letters, 1897, (6 folders) (Box 1, Folder 68-73)
  - Letters, 1898, (4 folders) (Box 1, Folder 74-77)
  - Letters, 1899, (11 folders) (Box 1, Folder 78-88)
  - Letters, 1900, (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 89-91)
  - Letters, 1901, (8 folders) (Box 1, Folder 92-99)
  - Letters, 1902, (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - Letters, 1903, (9 folders) (Box 2, Folder 4-12)
  - Letters, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Letters, 1905, (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
  - Letters, 1906, (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
  - Letters, 1907, (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
  - Letters, 1908, (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 20-23)
  - Letters, 1909, (5 folders) (Box 2, Folder 24-28)
  - Letters, 1910, (8 folders) (Box 2, Folder 29-36)
  - Letters, 1911, (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 37-40)
  - Letters, 1912, (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 41-43)
  - Letters, 1913, (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 44-46)
  - Letters, 1914, (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 47-50)
  - Letters, 1915, (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 51-54)
  - Letters, 1916, (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 55-58)
  - Letters, 1917, (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 59-61)
  - Letters, 1918, (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 62-64)
  - Letters, 1919, (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 65-66)
  - Letters, 1920, (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 67-68)
  - Letters, 1921, (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 69-71)
  - Letters, 1922, (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 72-74)
  - Letters, 1923, (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Letters, 1924, (4 folders; Oversized Material Housed in OV 11) (Box 3, Folder 4-7)
  - Letters, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Letters, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Letters, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Letters, 1928, (8 folders) (Box 3, Folder 11-18)
  - Letters, 1929, (7 folders) (Box 3, Folder 19-25)
  - Letters, 1930, (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 26-29)
  - Letters, 1931, (5 folders) (Box 3, Folder 30-34)
  - Letters, 1932, (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 35-38)
  - Letters, 1933, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 39-40)
  - Letters, 1934, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 41-42)
  - Letters, 1935, (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 43-45)
  - Letters, 1936, (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 46-49)
  - Letters, 1937, (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 50-52)
  - Letters, 1938, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 53-54)
  - Letters, 1939, (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 55-58)
  - Letters, 1940, (6 folders) (Box 3, Folder 59-64)
  - Letters, 1941, (5 folders) (Box 3, Folder 65-69)
  - Letters, 1942, (9 folders) (Box 3, Folder 70-78)
  - Letters, 1943, (9 folders) (Box 4, Folder 1-9)
  - Letters, 1944, (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 10-12)
  - Letters, 1945, (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 13-15)
  - Letters, 1946, (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 16-17)
  - Letters, 1947, (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
  - Letters, 1948, (4 folders) (Box 4, Folder 20-23)
  - Letters, 1949, (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 24-26)
  - Letters, 1950, (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 27-29)
  - Letters, 1951-1953 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Letters, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Letters, 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Letters, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Oversized Drawing of Plan of The Oaks Pool Enclosed in Letter, 1924, (from Box 3, Folder 7) (Box OV 11)
- Diaries, 1904-1949, Series 3:; (Box 4; 11 folders)
  There are seven diaries written by Joseph Lindon Smith and two by Corinna Smith during their travels in Egypt, Europe, and New Mexico.
  - Diary 1: Egypt, 1904-1905, (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 34-35)
  - Diary 2: Egypt, 1906-1907 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Diary 3: Europe, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Diary 4: Europe, 1918, (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 38-39)
  - Diary 5: Europe, 1918-1919 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Diary 6: New Mexico, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Diary 7: Persia (Persepolis), 1935 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Diary 8 by Corinna Putnam Smith: Beiram, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Diary 9 by Corinna Putnam Smith: Egypt, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Personal Business Records, 1647-1959, Series 4:; (Box 4, 10; 11 folders)
  Personal business records are found for both the Smith and Putnam families and for Joseph Lindon Smith, Corinna Smith, and their daughter Lois Smith. These include contracts, price lists, lists of securities, and miscellaneous receipts.
  - Legal Documents and Receipts for the Smith and Putnam Ancestors, 1647-1882, undated, (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 45-46)
  - Price Lists, 1894-1951 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Contract; Certificate of Shares in The Chelsea Pottery, 1895-1897 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1902-1959, (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 49-50)
  - Legal Documents Concerning Lois Lindon Smith, 1929-1936, (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 51-52)
  - Records of Stocks and Other Assets, 1938-1953, (3 folders; Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 4, Folder 53-55)
  - Oversized Statements of Trusteeship, 1951-1953, from Box 4, Folder 55 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Notes and Writings, 1783-1963, Series 5:; (Box 4-6; 2.0 linear feet)
  Notes and writings include engagement calendars, notebooks, lists of art work, lecture notes, minutes of meetings, notes on family history and travel, and numerous miscellaneous typescripts by the Smiths and others of essays and anecdotes about art, culture, travel, and many other topics. Also found are drafts for "Egypt - My Winter Home."
  - Engagement Calendar, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Engagement Calendar, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Notebook 1, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Notebook 2, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Notebook 3, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Notebook 4, undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Notebook 5, undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Notebook 6, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Notes on Asia, undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Notes on the Careers of Maya Archaeologists, undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Notes on Egypt, undated, (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 66-67)
  - Notes by Corinna Smith on "Egyptian Religion," undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Notes on Cecil Firth's Excavations, undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Notes on Mexico and Central America, undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Notes on Persia, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Notes on George Reisner, undated, (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 72-73)
  - Notes on Writers in Arabic, undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Autograph of Kit Carson; Autograph of Finnish Folk Singer Selma Borg, undated (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Lists of Art Work, 1931-1935, undated, (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 76-77)
  - Notes on Family History, 1945-1950 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Minutes of Meeting of Archeological Club, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Notes Describing Karnak, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Card File of Egyptian Art Work, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Remarks by Abd Essalam Hussein Delivered at the United States National Sculpture Society, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Broadcast for Egyptian Minister of Foreign Affairs, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Notes on Sakkara, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Minutes of Meeting Concerning Recommendations to Trustees, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Lecture Notes for "Journey Into the Past" for the Metropolitan Museum, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Minutes of Meeting of International Cooperation Administration, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Minutes of Meeting of the American Research Center in Egypt, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Anecdotes, undated, (9 folders) (Box 5, Folder 11-19)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1915-1946, undated, (4 folders) (Box 5, Folder 20-23)
  - Typescript "A Letter Addressed to Students of the Art of Painting and to his Professional Brethern," undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Manuscript "Amman and Air Force," undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Typescripts "The Dissenting Shi'a Sect" and "The Dream," undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Typescripts "Hadiths" and "Maya Civilization," undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Poems, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Manuscripts for Lectures on Portrait Painting, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Typescript "Three Dublin Artists," undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Typescript "Colored Statues" Describing Events in 1891, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to Greece in 1894, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Typescript "Primitive Travel" Describing Events in 1898, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Typescript "Quirigua and Copan" Describing Events in 1900; Typescript "With the Carnegie Staff at Chichen," undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Typescript "The Sarcophagus Found at Sidon" Describing Events in 1900, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Typescript "Baalbek" Describing Events in 1900; Typescripts "Palmyra" and "Petra" Describing Events in 1930, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to Japan in 1901, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to Japan in 1901 and 1910, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Typescript "Visits to Italy and England" Describing Events in 1907, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Manuscript Describing Travel to Egypt in 1909, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Typescript "A Visit to London" Describing Events in 1909, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to China in 1910, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Typescripts "The Ypres Salient," "Fort Douaumont," and "Fort De Vaux" Describing Events in 1918, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Typescript Describing Events in World War I, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Typescript "Things Done by Mr. Smith," 1918 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Typescript "Notes for Mr. Smith," 1918 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Typescript "Economic Crisis in Germany in October 1920," undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Typescript "Siam" Describing Events in 1921, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Manuscript "the Dieng Plateau" Describing Events in 1921, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to Java in 1921, undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to Bankok in 1921 and to Canton in 1923, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to Mexico in 1926, undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Typescript "Fido," 1926 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Manuscript "Excavations at Ur" Describing Events in 1930, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Typescript "Ur of the Chaldees and Other Way Stations" Describing Events in 1930, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Manuscript "Conflicting Ideas in Egypt of Today" Describing Events in 1931, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Typescripts "The Trip to Persepolis" Describing Events in 1935, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 57-58)
  - Manuscript Describing Travel to Egypt, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Typescript "Experience in Luxor" Describing Events in 1939, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Typescript "Journal Abydos" Describing Events in 1939, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 61-62)
  - Typescript for Lecture on Egypt for Bryn Mawr Benefit, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Report on Paintings of Sculpture and Architectural Details of the Ruins of Chichenitza, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Manuscript of Fund-Raising Address for the U.S.O., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Typescript "Sesostris Shrine at Karnak," 1947 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Manuscript Describing Travel to Egypt, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Transcript of Lecture on Egypt for Visiting Committee on Semitic and Egyptian Civilizations, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Report to Visiting Committee of Egyptian Department, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Typescript "The 'New' Egypt," 1949 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Typescript of Address to the Smithsonian Institution, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Typescript 1: "Egypt: My Winter Home," 1950, (12 folders) (Box 5, Folder 72-83)
  - Typescript 2: "Egypt: My Winter Home," 1950, (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 84-86)
  - Typescript 3: "Egypt: My Winter Home," 1950, (19 folders) (Box 6, Folder 1-19)
  - Miscellaneous Typescript Fragments, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Typescript "Joseph Lindon Smith" by Unidentified Author, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Typescript "Joseph Lindon Smith - In Memorium" by Unidentified Author, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Typescript by Unidentified Author Describing Travel to the Southwest United States, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Typescript "Garibaldi's Chapel" by Unidentified Author, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Manuscript "Gleanings" by Unidentified Author, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Typescript by Unidentified Author Concerning Gouda, the Shikari, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Typescript by Unidenfied Author Concerning Mark Twain's First Summer in Dublin, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Report Concerning Paul Cravath's Visit to Persepolis by the Field Director of the Iranian Expedition, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Typescript by Unidentified Author Concerning the British in Egypt in 1945, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Poems by Claude M. Fuess, 1933-1939 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Manuscript Concerning George Yarnell by Lois Anna Greene, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Manuscript "The Hallucinations of Grandfather Chad" by Lois Anna Greene, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Typescript "A Painter of Ancient Masterpieces: Joseph Lindon Smith" by Anne Webb Karnaghan, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Poem "Our Mudir" by Mahmud, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Poems by Rebecca London Malicheff, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Typescript "Studies in Nietzschean Cosmology" by George Morgan, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Typescript "The Ancient Maya" by Sylvanus G. Morley, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Manuscript "Description of a Fire Dance on the Navajo Reservation at Nara" by Frances Smith Otis, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Typescript "An Artist's Unique Estate at Dublin Lake, Dublin, N.H." by Harris Walter Reynolds, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Manuscript Concerning Travel to Asia by Denman Ross, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Manuscript "The Dying Sayings of John Jencks" Copied by Chad Smith, 1783 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Poems by Emma Greenleaf Smith, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Typescript "Madonna Del Fieno" by Hermann Voss, W. Bode, and Prof. Fischel, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Typescript "Eulogy of the Dog" by George Graham Vest, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous Poems, 1886-1947, undated, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 45-46)
  - Miscellaneous Writings by Others, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Theatrical Production Files, 1897-1950, Series 6:; (Box 6-7, 10; 1.2 linear feet)
  These files contain letters, notes, scripts, printed material, and photographs concerning plays, pageants, and masques written and/or produced by the Smiths for benefits, dedication, or anniversary celebrations. A notebook "Grandma Smith's Teatro Bambino" contains 2 photographs, a dedication ode by Thomas Wentworth Higginson, and a hand-written script.
  - Notebook "Grandma Smith's Teatro Bambino," undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Script for Play about the Spirit in the Fountain by Grandma Smith, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Untitled Play Scripts, undated, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 50-51)
  - Script for Andover Pageant, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Script for Play The Astrologer, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Script for Play Birds of a Feather, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Script for the "Buccaneer Play," undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Script for the "Christmas Play," undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Script for the "Circus Play," undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Script for Play The Columns of Catlin,undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Script for Play The Departure of Doris, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Script for Play Flora Enshrined, undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Script for Play How to Adventure, undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Script for Play The King of Kurosaki, undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Script for Play The Lay of the Last Egg, undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Script for Play The Legasee of the Hawaiian Buried Treasure, undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Script for Play Mexican Fiesta, undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Script for Play Monadnock Invaded, undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Script for Play Old Gobblegain, undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Script for Play Over the Rainbow, undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Introductory Remarks for Dance Performance by Sarita and Riccardo Romero, undated (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Script for Play A Shah of Persia, undated (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Script for Play The Silence of the Harp, undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Script for Play The Witch's Trunk, undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Programs for Play Alice in Wonderland,1897 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Script for Play Houri Kuri and Hurri Kurri, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Script for Play Danjuro No Tanjobi,1904 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Script for Watteau Fete, 1906 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Script for Play Jack Frost in Midsummer, 1908-1949, (Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Script for Play The Enchanted Forest, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Program for Pantomime and Dance Traumeswirren ("Dream Fancies"), 1909 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Script for the "Chinese Play," 1911 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - File for the Lancaster Pageant, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - File for the Pageant at Milton, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Script for Golden Jubilee Pageant at Buffalo Fine Arts Academy, 1912, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
  - File for the Tiffany Fete The Quest of Beauty, 1913-1916 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Script for Play Nuzhat-Fi-Bilad-El-Ajam, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Notes and Photographs from Masque of the Blue Garden, 1913, (Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Clippings and Photographs from Masque Sanctuary, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - File for the St. Louis Pageant and Masque, 1913-1914, (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 9-11)
  - File for Pageant Pan and the Star, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Script Notes for an Untitled Play, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - File for Masque The Tempest, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - File for Play As You Like It, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - File for Red Cross Pageant The Standard Bearers, 1916-1917 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - File for Pageant The Building of the Temple, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - File for Play Love of Country, 1917 and 1941 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - File for the Memphis Pageant, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - File for Play The Pearl and the Pirate, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - File for Pageant Once Upon a Time, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - File for the Amherst Centennial Pageant, 1921 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - File for the Submarine Ball, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - File for the Halloween Drama, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Script for Play The Loon's Laughter, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - File for an Untitled Tavern Play, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - File for Play The Lighthouse, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Program for Play The Enchanting Adventure, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - File for the Massachusetts Bay Colony Tercentenary Pageant, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - File for Play Brewster's Dark Pond, Presented for Amelia Earhart, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - File for Masque The Royal Gift, 1933, (7 folders) (Box 7, Folder 31-37)
  - File for the Play for the Century Association, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - File for Play Who could Imagine Such Happenings?,1934 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - File for the "Japanese Play," 1936 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - File for an Untitled Play, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - File for Play The Golden Key, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - File for Pageant The Children's Crusade, 1940, (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 43-45)
  - File for the Benefit for Hampshire, England, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Script for Pageant Voices Across the Sea, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - File for the Pageant Honoring Abbott Thayer, 1941-1943 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - File for an Untitled Play at the Club, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - File for Plays The Princess and the Peasant and The Old Chinese Artist Laughs at Last,1942 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - File for Pageant at Harvard, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - File for Benefit Auction, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - File for Play Columbia in Conference or Columbia on Strike, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - File for Pageant Children's Laughter, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - File for Pantomime A Chinese Landscape, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Script for the "Elizabethan Play," 1944 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - File for Play The President's Dilemma, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - File for Play John Singleton Copley, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - File for Play Through Magic Spectacles, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - File for Play Peace Greets Dublin, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - File for the Supper Party Play, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - File for Play The Warrior Comes Home, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - File for Play Then and Now, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - File for Play It's Time It Happened, 1949, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 64-65)
  - Script for the Golden Wedding Play, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - File for Play A Possible Solution, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Miscellaneous Notes and Writing Fragments for Theatrical Productions, undated, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 68-69)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs from Unidentified Theatrical Productions, undated, (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 70-72)
  - Oversized Musical Magazine Etude for Play Jack Frost in Midsummer,1949, (from Box 6, Folder 77) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Photographs of Masque of the Blue Garden, 1913, (from Box 7, Folder 7) (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Art Works, 1932-1943, Series 7:; (Box 8, 10; 8 folders)
  Art work includes a sketchbook with extensive notes, a painting, drawings by Joseph Lindon Smith, and prints by other artists.
  - Sketchbook/Notebook, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Drawings, 1932, undated, (4 folders;Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 8, Folder 2-5)
  - Illustrated Book The Juvenile Picture Book by E. G. Smith, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Drawings by Smith's Children, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Prints, 1933-1943, undated, (Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Oversized Drawings, undated, (from Box 8, Folder 6) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Oversized Painting on Panel, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Print, 1943, (from Box 8, Folder 8) (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Scrapbook, 1888-1901, Series 8:; (Box 8; 1 folder)
  A scrapbook contains clippings and an exhibition catalog from the St. Botolph Club.
  - Scrapbook, 1888-1901 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Printed Material, 1723-1963, Series 9:; (Box 8, OV 11; 0.8 linear feet)
  Printed material includes clippings, exhibition announcements and catalogs, press releases, programs, booklets, brochures, and books.
  - Clippings, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1759 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1898-1912 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1915-1919 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1920-1929 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1928-1930 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1931, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 16-17)
  - Clippings, 1932-1935 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Clippings, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Clippings, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 21)